heroesofnewerth.com 2018-12-26

# Heroes of Newerth - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy  
Frostburn Studios, LLC., heretofore "Frostburn Studios," provides this Privacy Statement to inform you of our privacy policy and practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

This Privacy Statement is notice of:

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website
  * The organization collecting the information
  * How the information is used
  * With whom the information may be shared
  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
  * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Frostburn Studios' control
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact Frostburn Studios by EMAIL at privacy@frostburnstudios.com.

Information Collection and Use  
Frostburn Studios is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Frostburn Studios collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

Cookies  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to participate in any of our Sweepstakes, Contests or monthly Drawings that take place. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

Log Files  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Sharing  
We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We partner with other parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services.

These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

Links  
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Frostburn Studios is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

Newsletter  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.

Surveys & Contests  
From time to time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

Tell-A-Friend  
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. Frostburn Studios will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Frostburn Studios stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may contact Frostburn Studios at policy@frostburnstudios.com to request the removal of this information from their database.

Correction/Updating Personal Information  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your email address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support.

Notification of Changes  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
